

CONTACT

annafuss@gmx.net linkedin.com/in/anna-c-fuss/ behance.net/annafuss +49 157 3945 1193

SKILLS

Competitive analysis
UX research (qualitative and quantitative methods)
Personas
Information architecture
User Flows and journeys
Wireframing
Prototyping
UI design
Responsive design
Workshop facilitation

TOOLS

Figma Adobe XD Miro Notion MS Office

LANGUAGES

German (native)
English (professional)
Swedish (intermediate)
French (beginner)

Anna Fuß

UX/UI Designer

PROFILE

UX/UI designer with a background in social science research and educational administration. Passionate about analytically driven and user-centered design processes. Experienced in communicating with different stakeholders from numerous teams and cultural origins. High capacity of problem solving, good organizational skills and attention to detail.

EXPERIENCES

UX/UI Designer, bytabo® GmbH, Bamberg

Nov 2022 - Present

- Design end-to-end experiences for a diverse range of mobile & web platforms
- Create User flows, personas, wireframes and high-fidelity prototypes
- Conduct user testing sessions to gather feedback and validate product features
- · Work closely with project managers, developers, and external stakeholders
- Facilitate design thinking workshops

International Student Exchange Coordinator University of Bamberg, Bamberg

Sep 2020 - Oct 2022

- offiversity of buffiberg, buffiberg
- · Processed applications and admissions for exchange students

· Advised and supported prospective and current exchange students

- Created and implemented a buddy program for local and international students
- Collaborated with several departments of the university to organize welcome events and a German preparatory course for new students

EDUCATION

UX/UI Design Certificate Career Foundry, Berlin/ remote

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023

- Completed > 850h immersive training to become a certified UX/UI Designer
- · Created three different hands-on projects during the program

Master of Arts in Sociology University of Bamberg

Apr 2018 - Aug 2020

- · Focus on qualitative and quantitative research methods
- Final grade: 1.2 (very good with distinction)

Bachelor of Arts in Sociology University of Bamberg & Åbo Akademi (Finland)

Oct 2013 - Mar 2018

- · Focus on quantitative research methods
- Final grade: 1.7 (good)